(Raj:)Well, I hope you saved room
for chocolate lava cake.
(Lakshmi:)Impressive.
(Lakshmi:)What goes into making something
like that?
Well, you start out by trying
to make chocolate soufflé.
(Raj:)And when it falls, you panic...
(Raj:)...quickly change the name,
and voilá, lava cake.
l bet our parents are dying to know
how things are going here.
(Raj:)Well, let's see.
Yep, three missed calls.
(Lakshmi:)Four missed calls, two text messages,
and a failed video chat.
- l win.
- Ha, ha.
So, what are we going to tell them?
- l'd like to tell them things are going well.
- Me too.
(Lakshmi:)But before we get their hopes up...
(Lakshmi:)...we should probably make sure
we're on the same page.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Raj:)What page are you on?
I'm on the one where I'm under
a lot of pressure from my parents...
(Lakshmi:)...to get married and settle down
and have a family.
(Lakshmi:)And I'm going to do it
so they don't find out I'm gay.
Say again?